

Ossiris Lynch

- North Las Vegas, NV 89084 \$\frac{1}{2}\$ 7029727099
- ossirislynch1@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Talented Manager with expert team leadership. I'am self motivated and driven. I look forward to planning my days and I developed exceptional organizational skills during successful my career. Smoothly equip employees to independently handle daily functions and meet customer needs. Diligent trainer, mentor and a strong leader and problem-solver. Dedicated to streamlining operations to decrease costs and promote organizational efficiency. Uses independent decision-making skills and sound judgment to positively impact company success.

SKILLS

- Business Development
- Team Leadership
- Emergency Response
- Team Development

- Operations Management
- Teamwork and Collaboration
- Business Administration

WORK HISTORY

MANAGER

10/2023 to CURRENT

Kulture Ink And Kutz | 4753 S. Maryland Parkway

- Managing full operation of the barbershop and overseeing two apprentices.
- Maintaining the requirement regulations of Nevada State Barber Board and Health and Sanitation Department.
- Making sure that all licenses are up to date and in good standing with the Secretary of State, Clark County business department and the Fire Department.
- And making sure customers are taken get the best experience when leaving the barbershop.

OWNER/BARBER

11/2020 to 10/2023

9th Island Barber Shop | Las Vegas

- I owned and managed 9th island barber shop. Along with being the manager of the shop and being updated with all licenses and permits, I also covered the cost.
- Negotiated contracts with suppliers for better pricing and terms, reducing overall costs for the business.
- I have experienced the true meaning of a business owner. The build out of the shop was the most overwhelming however I have gained the knowledge and experience in project management, time management, and risk assessment.
- Managing individuals ranging from architect, electricians, plumbers,

framers, painters, and flooring crew I developed a keen sense of being on time.

- I managed a total of seven barbers throughout our daily operations.
- Scheduled employees for shifts, taking into account customer traffic and employee strengths.
- Recruited, hired, and trained initial personnel, working to establish key internal functions and outline scope of positions for new organization.
- Prepared bank deposits and handled business sales, returns, and transaction reports.
- Successfully navigated challenging economic conditions by making informed decisions that protected the business's financial stability.
- Established foundational processes for business operations.

OWNER/OPERATOR TRUCK DRIVER

03/2020 to 04/2023

Send And Receiving LLC | Las Vegas, NV

- Managed day-to-day business operations.
- Established strong working relationships with dispatchers, resulting in improved coordination and scheduling.
- Managed financial aspects of business operations including budgeting, expense tracking, invoice processing, and tax filing.
- Assessed vehicle in fleet, identifying those requiring immediate repair work and minor maintenance.
- Clearly communicated with dispatchers to give updated information on estimated times of arrival and latest road conditions.
- Maximized payload capacity while adhering to legal weight restrictions through careful selection of cargo assignments.

EDUCATION

Nevada First Barber School, Las Vegas, NV

08/2010

Barber School of Louisiana, Baton Rouge, LA

04/2007

High School Diploma

06/1998

Rancho High School, Las Vegas, NV

LANGUAGES (

Tagalog

Native or Bilingual